乔伊  你可以慢一点吗
Joey, would you slow down?
报纸不会在凌晨一点卖光的
They're not gonna be sold out of papers at 1:00 in the morning.
我好兴奋  我从来没有被剧评过
I'm excited. I've never gotten reviewed before.
你演的国王好棒  我超欣赏的  真的
You were so amazing as the king. I'm really impressed. I was.
不过你知道吗
But you know what?
你得考虑一下  下次要穿内裤
You might wanna consider wearing underwear next time.
你坐上王位时  看得到你的…
Because when you sat on your throne, you could kind of see your...
皇家物件
...royal subjects.
在这里
Here it is. Here it is.
〝唯一比没脑幼稚的导演糟的
"The only thing worse than the mindless adolescent direction...
是乔伊·崔比亚尼对国王不熟练的诠释〞
...was Joseph Tribbiani's disturbingly unskilled portrayal of the king."
听好  这只是一个人的主观意见
Okay, look. That is one guy's opinion.
好吗  菲比  念你的  好
All right? Pheebs, read yours. - Okay.
〝唯一比没脑幼稚的导演糟的〞
"The only thing worse than the mindless, adolescent direction..."
谁有别的报纸
Does anybody have one from a different paper?
罗斯  念你的
Ross, read yours.
我不要
I don't want to.
乔伊  他们不晓得自己在说什么
Joey, honey, they don't know what they're talking about.
也许他们知道
Maybe they do.
我在这行已经十年了  还一无所成
I've been doing this 10 years and I haven't gotten anywhere.
一定有原因的
There's gotta be a reason.
别这样  你还是在付出阶段
Come on, man, you're just, uh, paying your dues.
不是  真的是太困难了
No, no, no. It's too hard.
真不值得  我不干了
It's not worth it. I quit.
什么  你疯了
What? That's crazy.
等等  等等
Wait, wait one minute. Wait a minute.
包你听了会回心转意的
I believe this will change your mind.
〝凭着平凡的剧本  乔伊·崔比亚尼成功地达到全新水平的…〞
"In a mediocre play, Joseph Tribbiani was able to achieve brilliant new levels of..."
153页继续
Continued on page 153.
〝烂透了〞
"...sucking."
《老友记》 第二季 第10集: 他的主修是牙龈
Friends S02E10: The One With Russ
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
我小时候  梦想当个兽医
When I was little, I wanted to be a veterinarian.
然而我发现我必须把手伸进牛的什么的里面
But then I found out you have to put your hands into cows and stuff.
嗨
Hi.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）
就是个水深火热的一天
Yeah, just a tough day at work, you know?
（制片：贝西·伯恩斯）
剑龙倒下  困住一个孩子
Stegosaurus fell over, trapped a kid.
我知道这件外套  这是好笑巴比的外套
I know this jacket. This is Fun Bobby's jacket.
他在哪儿  他在这儿  对吧
Where is he? What? He's here, isn't he?
也许  别耍我
Maybe.  Don't toy with me.
盖勒  你好  好笑巴比
Geller! Hey, Fun Bobby.
（编剧：艾拉·安德里德）
你最近都在上健身房吗
Whoa, hey. You been working out?
才没有
Not at all.
我爱这家伙
I love this guy.
我很开心你和我妹妹和好了
I was so psyched to hear you're back with my sister.
（导演：汤玛斯·史蓝姆）
我们两个都是  我有错过什么吗  快招
You and me both. So, what'd I miss? Come on.
我们想让乔伊开心起来
Oh. We were trying to make Joey feel better.
你要不要我把你举起来  不要  我很好  真的
Hey, do you need me to pick you up? - No, I'm all right, man, really.
我要举你起来喽
No, I'm picking you up.
说真的  我不需要你…
Hey, no, seriously. I don't need you to...
好耶  还是有用  很好
All right, it still works.Okay.
我走之前  还有谁需要被举起来的
Now, before I go, does anybody else need to be picked up?
我还是走吧
I'm still gonna go.
晚点见  宝贝
Okay, I'll see you later, babe. Ah.
现在有公开亲热镜头  你们可以转头
Public display of affection coming up. You can avert your eyes.
唔
Mm.
再见  拜
See you. Bye.
好笑巴比真棒
Fun Bobby is so great.
可不是吗
Oh, isn't he?
我真的在想或许跟他是有未来的  他让我很开心
I really think this time it may work with him. I mean, he makes me feel so good.
这两个月我感觉很糟  没工作  没男朋友
And I've been feeling so lousy, you know, no job, no boyfriend.
现在至少杯子是半满的
Well, at least my cup is half full.
〝半满的爱〞
Half full of love.
为了庆祝我们的两礼拜纪念日  他周末要带我去他表弟的小木屋
And for our two-week anniversary, he's gonna take me to his cousin's cabin.
爱的小木屋
Cabin of love.
我们今晚喝掉了很多红酒
We went through a lot of wine tonight, you guys.
真的  我才喝了两杯  我才喝一杯
Really? I only had two glasses. I just had a glass.
两杯  我一杯
Two. I had one glass.
我用这个可爱的…
I had about a mug full in this lovely...
〝我在自然历史博物馆嗨翻了〞 马克杯喝了一杯
..."I got boned at the Museum of Natural History" mug.
所以那是  两瓶吗
Okay, so that's, what? Two bottles.
但是我们喝掉了五瓶
And yet somehow we went through five?
哇
CHANDLER: Whoa.
噢
Oh.
那又怎样  他今晚喝多了一点
So what? So he drank a lot tonight.
但你知道  现在我想起来…
Yeah, but, you know, now that I think about it...
好笑巴比手上永远都有一杯酒
...I don't think I've ever seen Fun Bobby without a drink in his hand.
对啊
PHOEBE: Yeah. Ooh, ooh, yeah, you know?
你们有注意到  他故事的开始总是
Did you notice how he always starts his stories with, um:
〝我当时好醉〞或是 〝我们都喝醉了〞
"Okay, I was so wasted," or, "Oh, we were so bombed."
又或是〝我醒来时发现我在康州的一个垃圾箱里〞
Or, um, "So I wake up and I'm in this Dumpster in Connecticut."
摩妮卡  你们约会时他有没有喝过酒
Monica, have you ever been with him when he wasn't drinking?
只是恰巧而已  我们去的地方都会喝酒的
Well, we just happen to go to a lot of places where you might drink.
去个品酒会  总不能不喝吧
I mean, how do you go to a wine-tasting without having a drink?
或是夜店  或…
Or to a club, or to the...
动物园
...zoo.
（中央咖啡厅）
瑞秋  这里面有脱脂牛奶吗
Rach, does this have nonfat milk?
不知道  你为什么不试一下
Um, I don't know, why don't you taste it?
没有
Mm. No.
太晚了  你已经喝到了
Oh, well, too late, you already had some.
我们来把它变成爱尔兰咖啡怎么样
What do you say we make these, uh, coffees Irish?
蛋糕
Um, cake.
对  我们想要来点蛋糕
Yeah, we're gonna... We're gonna get some cake.
你知道吗  最近你把很多东西都变爱尔兰式的了
You know, it seems like you've been making an awful lot of stuff Irish lately.
我也可以做比利时式的  但松饼很难塞进酒瓶子里
I would make them Belgian, but the waffles are hard to get into that flask.
巴比
Bobby.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
也许这不关我的事  也许是  我不知道
Look, maybe this is none of my business, or maybe it is, I don't know.
我有点担心你
But, um, I'm kind of worried about you.
这不是第一次有人和我提这件事
Okay, look, this isn't the first time somebody said something to me about this.
我总是找藉口 像〝我只是交际一下〞
But, I don't know, I always made excuses, like "I'm just a social drinker."
或〝今天是国旗日！〞
Or "Hey, come on, it's Flag Day."
你想说什么
So, what are you saying now?
我想说的是…
I guess I'm saying...
我会试着戒酒
...I'll try and quit.
你这样担心我  我很窝心
I kind of like that you worry about me.
发生什么事啦
So, what's going on?
我会试着戒酒
I am gonna try and quit drinking.
为什么
Oh. Why?
大家好  嘿
Hey.  Hey.
嗨  大家好
Hey. Hey.
猜猜谁又东山再起了
Guess who's back in show business.
洛恩·格林
Ooh, ooh. Lorne Greene?
菲比  不是  你知道为什么吗  因为他死掉了
No, Pheebs. You know why? Because he's dead.
不会吧
Oh, no.
我想这好像有点苦乐参半…
Okay, I guess this is gonna seem bittersweet now...
是乔伊  就是他
...but Joey, that's who.
真的  太好了
Oh, yay! Really?
我经纪人才打来  叫我去《我们的日子》试镜
My agent just called me with an audition for Days of our Lives.
帅呆了
Kick ass.
我们得庆祝  应该开个肥皂剧主题派对
We have to celebrate. We should do a soap opera theme.
对  我们可以一起上床  然后其中一个人要失去记忆
Hey, yeah. We could all sleep together, and then one of us could get amnesia.
瑞秋  你几点下班  我们今晚有节目
Rach, what time do you get off? We're all gonna do something tonight.
事实上  我下班了  但是我已经有约了
Uh, well, actually, I'm already done. Ahem. But I kind of got plans.
你有其他的朋友
You have other friends?
我有个约会
Yeah, I, uh... I have a date.
什么  跟一个男人
What?  With a man?
怎么  我有约会很奇怪吗
What? What is so strange about me having a date?
那罗斯怎么办
What about Ross?
你还在为列单子的事在跟他生气吗
Are you still mad at him because he made that list about...?
没有  我才没有生气
No, no, I'm not mad at him.
我再也不会对他有什么
I'm not really anything at him anymore.
你在讲什么  我不知道
What are you talking about? I don't know.
不管我以前怎么感觉  我…现在不了
Whatever I was feeling, I'm... not.
你们就只差那一步
But you guys came so close.
我知道  很抱歉  伙计们  你们得习惯…
Oh, I know. I'm sorry, you guys. You're gonna have to get used to the fact...
我不再和罗斯约会
...that I will not be dating Ross.
他来了  嗨
Here he is. Hi.
各位  这是洛斯
Guys, this is Russ.
大家好
Hi.
（伊斯特李奥纳德经纪公司）
不  我不是说你没才华  你非常有才华
No, no, no. I'm not saying you're not talented. You're very talented.
只是那只鸟死了后  剩下的戏就很少了
It's just that with the bird dead and all, there's very little act left.
甜心  饶了我吧  我们晚一点联络
Oh, honey, give me a break, will you? Oh, oh. I'll talk to you later.
我最喜爱的客户
Well, there's my favorite client.
达令  试镜试得如何
So tell me, darling, how was the audition?
很不错  我礼拜四还要复试
Well, I think it went pretty well. I got a callback for Thursday.
乔伊  你看过我心醉神迷吗
Joey. Have you ever seen me ecstatic?
没有  准备好  那你见识看看
No. Well, here it is.
有件事我想和你谈一谈
Okay. Uh, listen, there's something I want to talk to you about.
那个选角的女人  罗莉很讨人喜欢吧
The network casting lady...  Oh, isn't Lori a doll?
对  她很不错
Yeah, yeah, she's great.
我感觉她好像对我有那么一点点意思
But I kind of got the feeling that she was sort of coming on to me.
我肯定拿得到那个角色的  如果我  你也知道的
And I definitely would get the part if I were to, you know...
看我是否要派我的“小将军”出马
lf I would have sent the little general in. Oh.
知道了  让我打个电话
I see. Well, I'm just gonna put in a call here...
我们来把事情搞清楚  解决掉
...and we'll find out what's going on and straighten it out.
喂  麻烦转罗莉
Yeah, hi. Lori, please.
喂  达令
Hi, darling.
乔伊·崔比亚尼  当那计程车司机适合吧
So how about Joey Tribbiani for the part of the cab driver?
他超棒的  对不对
Isn't he terrific?
啊-哦
Uh-huh.
好  美女  晚一点再说喽
Okay, doll, talk to you later.
没错  你得跟她上床
Yeah, you're gonna have to sleep with her.
怎么啦  好笑巴比
What's the matter? Fun Bobby.
怎么  他不是戒酒了
What? Isn't he sober?
他还算清醒
Oh, he's sober all right.
结果是  好笑巴比  有趣是有原因的
Just turns out that Fun Bobby was fun for a reason.
知道了
Ah. Okay.
来喽  甜心
All right, here you go, sweetie.
谢谢  你们想听笑话吗
Thanks. You wanna hear something funny?
天啊  当然
Oh, God, yes.
格林威治村过了午夜  五金行就关门了
There are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
很好笑
That is funny.
有一晚我得买支铁锤…
I needed to buy a hammer the other night...
我就在附近逛逛
...and I'm out walking around the neighborhood.
显然地…
But apparently...
格林威治村过了午夜所有五金行就关门了
...there are no hardware stores open past midnight in the Village.
甜心  你现在不是有个面试
Uh, say, honey, don't you have to be at your interview?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
再见  拜
See you guys.Bye...
超级无趣的巴比
...ridiculously dull Bobby.
我的天  没那么糟啦
Oh, my God.  He's not that bad.
没那么糟  你没听到那铁锤的故事吗
Not that bad? Did you not hear the hammer story?
不要那么挑剔就好了
Okay, okay, don't get all squinky.
也许是要在场才能体会的事
Maybe it was just the kind of story where you had to be there.
但是我会在场
But I'm gonna be there.
我下半辈子都会在场
For the rest of my life.
我没办法跟他分手  是我要他戒酒的
I can't break up with him. I made him quit drinking.
他因为我而无趣   别这么说
He's dull because of me.  All right, don't say that.
也许他一直都很无聊   你只是…
He's probably always been dull. You just, you know...
解放了他
...set it free.
嗨  嗨  罗斯
Hi. Hey, Ross. Ah.
嗨  洛斯
Hi, Russ.
再打扫两张桌子我们就可以走了  好吗
I've just got two more tables to clean, and then we'll go, okay?
好  我就坐在这里…
Okay. I'll just sit here and, uh...
跟你的…
...chat with your, uh...
好朋友聊天
...friend-type people.
瑞秋  你好
Rachel? Um, hi.
嗨  好
Hi.  Okay.
你知道你在做什么  对吧
So you know what you're doing, right?
当女服务生
Ha, ha. Waitressing?
不是  我是指…
Well, yeah. But, no. I mean, um...
洛斯没有让你想起某人
Doesn't Russ just remind you of someone?
鲍伯·萨格特   对哦
Huh. Bob Saget?  Oh, yeah.
不…  你好
No, no, no. Oh, oh.  Hi.
天啊
Oh, my, oh.
怎么了
What...? What's wrong?
我   很好  她不开心是因为…
I... Okay. She's just upset because she, uh...
她今早把一只蜘蛛涂在吐司上了
She buttered a spider into her toast this morning.
嗯-哼
Mm-hm.
好吧
All right.
听着  菲比  没关系的
Listen, Pheebs. This is gonna be okay.
罗斯  洛斯  洛斯  罗斯
Ross, Russ. Russ, Ross.
你好  你好
Hi.  Hi.
你是瑞秋的朋友
Are you a, uh, friend of Rachel's?
我是
Yes. Yes, I am.
你是瑞秋的朋友
Are you a, uh, friend of Rachel's?
事实上  我算是…
Actually, I'm, uh, kind of a...
是她的…
...you know...
瑞秋的…
...a date-type thing...
约会对象
...of Rachel's.
约会  对  她的约会对象
A date? Yeah. I'm her date.
你是…
Oh. Oh, you're, uh...
你是她的约会对象
Oh, you're the date.
这事实上是件好事
You know, this is actually good...
因为万一我们失去罗斯  还有个备胎
...because if we ever lose Ross, we have a spare.
你就是那个古生物学家
Oh. You are the, uh, paleontologist.
是的  我是  而你是…
Yes. Yes, I am. And you are a...
牙周病专科医师
Periodontist.
瞧  他们之间的差别简直是黑夜…
See? Now they're as different as night and...
和更黑的夜
...later that night.
我去买个饮料
Well, I am going to, uh, get a beverage. Heh.
很高兴认识你  幸会
Uh, it was nice, uh, meeting you. Ditto.
我  见过洛斯了
I, uh... Well, I met Russ.
噢
Oh.
我不知道我们…边跟别人交往
Hey, I didn't know we were, uh, seeing other people.
我们之间又没在约会  所以
Well, we're not seeing each other, so... Huh.
只是让你知道一下  博物馆里有个女人…
Well, uh, for your information, there's a woman at the museum...
负责蛾类还有其他…
...who's curator of moths and other, uh...
有翅膀的生物
...winged things...
她很明显地喜欢我  就像是…
...who's, uh, let it be known that she is drawn to me, much like a...
你知道的
...you know. Ahem.
我一直试着保持距离  但如果你是这样…
Well, so far I've been keeping her at bay, but, uh, if this is the deal...
对  我就要这样
Yeah, this is the deal.
好  祝你今晚玩得愉快  谢谢
Okay, well, um, have a nice evening. Thank you.
洛斯  你准备好了吗   好了
Russ, are you ready? Yeah.
再见  再见
Bye. Bye.
她在约会
She's dating?
对  但你看到她在跟谁约会吗
Yes. Yes, but did you see who she was dating?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你看不出来  看到什么
Do you not see it? See what?
我真不知道她看上那呆子哪一点
I don't know what she sees in that goober.
他需要…不知道
It takes him, what? Like, I don't know, uh...
一个礼拜来讲完一句话
...hello, a week to get out a sentence?
很讨厌  对吧
Yeah, it's annoying, isn't it?
对啊
Yeah.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
哇  哇
Whoa, whoa.
我猜你是没拿到那个角色…
I'm guessing you didn't get the part...
还是意大利打电话来说它饿了
...or, uh, Italy called and said it was hungry?
那角色是我的  如果我想要的话
Well, the part's mine if I want it.
我的天
Oh, my God.
没错  如果我愿意和选角的女士上床的话
Yeah. If I'm willing to sleep with the casting lady.
我的
Oh, my...
天
...God?
这十年来我一直在等像这样的机会  钱德  十年耶
Ten years I've been waiting for a break like this, Chandler. Ten years.
我是说“我们的日子”那真的会在电视上播出
I mean, Days of our Lives. That's actually on television.
你想怎么做
So, what are you gonna do?
我想我可以和她上床  但是…
I guess I could sleep with her. I mean...
我怎么能那样做
How can I do that?
我有本立体书  教我关于性的一切
Well, I've got a pop-up book that told me everything I needed to know.
我从来没为了一个角色跟人睡过
I've never slept with someone for a part.
那她是…
Well, is she...?
抱歉
Sorry.
她好看吗  是的
Is she good-looking? Yeah.
她很迷人  如果我在哪个夜店遇上她…
She's totally good-looking. I mean, if I met her in a bar or something...
我会想给她买早餐
...I'd be buying her breakfast.
你知道  跟她上床之后
You know, after having slept with her.
也许这没什么大不了的
You know, maybe this isn't such a big deal.
依我看  你不但得到一份好工作  还可以跟她上床
I mean, the way that I see it is, you get a great job and you get to have sex.
你知道  也许再加上一棵树跟胖子就像圣诞树了
You know? Throw in a tree and a fat guy, and you've got Christmas.
我只是不希望那样得到这份工作  你知道吗
I just... I just don't think that I want it that way though, you know?
我是说  如果有一天我成名了
I mean, let's say I do make it, all right?
我会总怀疑那到底是因为我的才华
I'm always gonna look back and wonder if it was because of my talent...
还是因为  你知道的  我的“小将军”。
...or because of, you know, the little general.
你以前不是叫它“小少校”的吗
Didn't you used to call it the little major?
是啊  但在上过丹妮丝·帝马可后  我给它升级了
Yeah, but after Denise DeMarco, I had to promote it.
两位要不要来一杯酒吗
Can I get you something from the bar?
好  我要来一杯
Yes, I would like something.
不要  谢谢
No. No, thank you.
如果你想喝  我没问题  我得习惯
No, if you want a drink, it's okay with me. I've gotta get used to it.
不要  说真的  我会觉得不对劲
No, no, really. I wouldn't feel right about it.
来杯水好了  谢谢
Just some water, please.
我冰箱的灯熄了  威士忌加冰块跟柠檬皮
So the light went out in my refrigerator.Scotch on the rocks with a twist.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这游戏很有趣吧  罗斯
Hey, we're having some fun now, huh, Ross?
再做一个吗  洛斯
Wanna do another one? Huh, Russ?
好  11个字母
Okay. Eleven letters...
原子元素101号  字尾是〝ium〞
...atomic element number 101, ends in "ium."
是镝   镝
Dysprosium. Ha, ha. Dysprosium.
试试钔吧
Try mendelevium.
二号答对了
And weenie number two has it.
除非直九的“白缎之夜”是“杜迪蓝调”唱的
Unless of course 9 Down, "Nights in White Satin" was sung by the Doody Blues.
你没看懂吗  你真的没看懂
You don't see it? You actually don't see it?
什么事  甜心  你在和罗斯交往
What? Okay, honey, you're dating Ross.
不对  菲比  我在和洛斯约会
No, Pheebs, I'm dating Russ.
洛斯就是罗斯  洛斯  罗斯
Russ is Ross. Russ, Ross.
史帝夫  大夫
Steve, sleeve.
好没有人名字叫大夫
Okay, no one is named sleeve.
菲比  你到底在讲什么
Phoebe, what the hell are we talking about?
除了他们的名字相似外  我很抱歉  我看不到你看到的
Other than their names being similar, I'm sorry, I do not see what you're seeing.
只是让你知道  是行家  不是老手
For your information, it's a card sharp, not a card shark.
你错到底了
You could not be more wrong.
你可以试  但你不会成功的
You could try, but you would not be successful.
好  我先去倒杯咖啡  在你们开始互戳眼睛前
Okay, I'm gonna get some more coffee before the pinching and eye-poking begins.
我知道你的问题是什么了  你知道
I know what your problem is. Oh, you do, do you?
你在吃醋
Mm-hm. You're jealous.
吃什么醋
Uh, of what?
你嫉妒我是真正的医生
You're jealous because I'm a real doctor.
你是牙龈医生
Hey, you're a doctor of gums.
那是人能够钻研的最小的人体器官
That's the smallest body part you can major in.
就只是  第一天  正确用牙线 第二天  拿到文凭
It's like, day one, floss. Day two, here's your diploma.
你听好  不要
Now, you listen... No, no.
让我说完  不  让我说完
Let me finish. No, let me finish.
不  你让我说
No, you let me fin...
嗨  嗨
Hi.  Hi.
呕
Ew.
呕  呕  呕
Ew, ew, ew.
乔伊告诉过你  他要怎么做吗  没有
Did Joey say what he was gonna do? No.
我不认为他知道
I don't even think he knew.
你会为了一份好工作跟某人上床吗
Hey, would you sleep with somebody to get a great job?
不知道  我得看跟谁睡
I don't know. Who would I have to sleep with?
我
Me.
我为什么要跟你上床
Why would I have to sleep with you?
这是我的游戏  你要这工作还是不要
It's my game. You want the job or not?
嗨  嘿
Hi.  Hey.
早安  你要上哪儿去
Good morning. Where you going?
巴比跟我要去度周末  记得吗
Bobby and I are going away for the weekend. Remember?
哦
Oh.
这些酒又是怎么回事
What's with all the bottles of liquor?
怎么了  巴比又开始喝酒
What's going on? Is, uh, Bobby drinking again?
这不是给他的  是我要喝的
Oh, no, this is not for him. This is for me.
这样  他会很清醒  我也会觉得他的鞋带故事有趣多了
That way, he's still sober, but I find his stories about shoelaces more amusing.
老天  他连敲门都这么无聊
Ugh, God. Even his knock is boring.
我马上就准备好了  我能和你谈一下吗
Hi. I'll be ready in just a second. Uh, could I talk to you a minute?
好啊
Sure.
这真的很难开口  老天  你又醉了吗
This is really hard for me to say. Oh, God. You fell off the wagon.
不是
Oh, no, no.
是有关你的
It's about you.
我怎么了
What about me?
我想你可能有酗酒问题
I think you may have a drinking problem.
什么  这些
What, these?
不是  这是消毒伤口用的
No, these are, um, for cuts and scrapes.
我现在无法扯入一段相互依赖的关系当中  好吗
Look, I am just not strong enough to be in a codependent relationship right now.
该死
Oh, shoot.
不管怎么样  我希望我们还是朋友
Well, anyway, I hope we can be friends.
好
Okay.
保重
Take care.
好  你也保重  再见
Okay. You too. Bye.
怎么了
What happened?
我们分手了
Well, we kind of broke up.
噢
Aw.
这些酒谁要
Does anybody want these?
我拿一瓶
I'll take one.
有时候我喜欢拿这种东西  假装我是个巨人
Sometimes I like to hold stuff like this and pretend I'm a giant.
嘿  复试如何
Hey.  Hey. How'd the callback go?
真让人不敢相信  我到了那儿  她就对我上下其手
Ugh, it was unbelievable. I walked in there and she was all over me.
那你怎么做   我办不到
So, what did you do? - Well, I couldn't do it.
我告诉她我不想那样得到角色  做得好
I told her I didn't want the part that way.  Good for you.
等等  等等  我离开她办公室之后…
Oh, wait, wait, wait. But then after I left her office...
她追我追到电梯  要给我一个更重要的角色
...she caught up with me at the elevator and offered me an even bigger part.
然后呢
So, and?
所以你们现在看到的是德瑞克·雷莫瑞  神经外科医生
So you are now looking at Dr. Drake Ramoray, neurosurgeon...
至少四集出场机会
...recurring in at least four episodes.
太棒了
All right!
太好了  我去洗澡了
All right, I gotta go shower.
大家好
Hi.
嘿  嗨
Oh, hey. Hi.
我想你们都听说了  瑞秋甩了我
I guess you guys heard Rachel dumped me.
我很遗憾  老兄
Yeah, I'm sorry, man.
她只说我让她想起另外一个人
All she said was that I remind her too much of somebody.
你们知道她是指谁吗
You have any idea who she's talking about?
我知道  是鲍伯·萨格特
Oh, I do. It's Bob Saget.
她讨厌他
She hates him.Oh.
嘿   你好  茱莉
Hey. Hey, Julie.
最近好吗
Hey, how are you doing?
不知道  没有罗斯  真的感觉有些奇怪
Oh. I don't know. I mean, it's definitely weird not being with Ross...
但是我想我还好
...but I guess I'm doing okay.
事实上  我带了一些他的东西……
Actually, I've got some of his stuff that he, um...